BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.873: United Underwear Contractors Association AND Greater Blouse and Skirt Contractors Association and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62 AND Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Code no.1641: Union Carbide Corporation and Chemicals and Crafts Union, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Code no.1642: Union Carbide Corporation and Texas Metal Trades Council, AFL-CIO, 1961-1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Code no.1643: American Cyanamid Company and International Chemical Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 143, 1961-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Code no.1645: E.R. Squibb and Sons Chemical Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 8-843, 1961-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Code no.1646: Parke, Davis and Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 7-176, 1959- 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Code no.1647: Colgate-Palmolive Company and Employees Association, Inc. of Colgate Palmolive Company, 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Code no.1648: Colgate-Palmolive Company and International Chemical Workers' Union, Local 15, 1959-1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Code no.1649: Lever Brothers Company and International Chemical Workers' Union, Local 217, 1961-1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Code no.1652: Revlon, Inc. and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Code no.1655: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and The Chemical Industrial Union, 1956-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Code no.1657: Hercules Powder Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 3-495, 1960- 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Code no.1659: Allied Chemical Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12330, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Code no.1660: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and Transparent Film Workers, Inc., 1960-1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Code no.1661: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and The Buffalo Yerkes Film Union, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Code no.1662: Shulton, Inc. and General Warehousemen's Union (Teamsters), Local 892, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Code no.1663: American Enka Corporation and United Textile Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 815, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Code no.1664: Allied Chemical Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, Local 13942, 1963-1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Code no.1665: Hercules, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 2-591, 1963-1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Code no.1667: Miles Laboratories and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12273, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Code no.1670: E.R. Squibb and Sons (Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation) and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 8-138, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Code no.1673: Union Carbide Corporation and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, Local 656, 1966-1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Code no.1676: Union Carbide Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 598, 1965- 1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Code no.1677: Celanese Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1957-1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Code no.1678: Hercules, Inc. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Local 884, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Code no.1680: The NVF Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 487, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)